Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Maps, Series I
  - Topographic Maps. United States., 000003
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Yates scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000258
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Yates NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000259
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Yates NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000260
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Yates SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000261
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Cannon Ball scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000271
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Cannon Ball NW scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10037.8/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000272
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Cannon Ball SE scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000273
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Cannon Ball SW scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000274
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Red Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5/W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000308
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Red Butte NW scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000309
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hannover` scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000324
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hannover NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000325
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazen East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000329
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazen West scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000332
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Beulah scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000498
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Stanton scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000557
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Trenton SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000609
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Buford scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10352.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000610
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Watford City scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10400/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000619
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: McClusky scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10200/ Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000620
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Zap scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000208
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Garrison Dam South scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000266
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazen NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000330
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazen NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10137./7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000331
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Beulah NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000499
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Beulah NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000500
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: White Earth Quadrangle scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000579
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Ross NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10237.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000582
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Glen Ullin SW scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000269
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hailstone Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000321
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Judson scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000354
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: New Salem NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000451
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: New Salem NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000452
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Figure 4 Ranch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10245/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000573
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mandaree scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10237.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000588
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lookout Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000194
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lookout Butte SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000195
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Rice scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10030/7.5Q Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000257
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grassna scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000317
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grassna NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000318
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grassna NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000319
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Half Timber Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000322
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Huff scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000337
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Huff NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000338
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kiefer Buttes scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000348
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Temvik scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000417
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Timmer scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000419
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Froelich scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000424
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Pamplin Hills scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000433
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Porcupine scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000443
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Barren Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000487
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Shields SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000515
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Selfridge scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000522
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Selfridge SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000523
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Solen SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000537
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Shields scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000542
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazelton NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000545
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazelton SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000546
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazelton SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000547
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hazelton scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000548
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Strasburg scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000554
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hell Hollow scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10707.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1971; 000611
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Medicine Butte SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000206
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Medicine Butte SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000207
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wheeler Hills scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000218
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fort Clark SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000256
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Garrison Dam North scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000265
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Center scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000275
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Coffin Buttes scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000276
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Coleharbor scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000277
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Crown Butte scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000280
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Crown Butte NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000281
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Crown Butte Lake scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000285
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Red Butte SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000310
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Riverdale North scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4730-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000314
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Riverdale South scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000315
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hannover scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000323
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Leith scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000357
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Carson SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000396
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Pretty Rock Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000414
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Pretty Rock Butte SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000415
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Otter Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000430
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Paradise Flats scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000434
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Pitt Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000438
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Nelson Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000444
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: New Leipzig South scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000449
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Round Top scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000509
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sheep Creek Dam scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000518
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sweet Briar scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1972; 000551
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hebron scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10200/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1973; 000602
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: New Hradec North scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10252.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1973; 000603
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Indian Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10207.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1973; 000604
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grassy Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10307.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1974; 000612
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Index to Top Maps of ND scale: 1: 1000 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N46-W104 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1974; 000624
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mc Kenzie scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000202
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mc Kenzie NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000203
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wing SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000211
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wing SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000212
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Regan SE scale: 1: 24000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000312
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lake Geneva scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000340
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Keever Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000350
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Linton NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000372
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Clear Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000394
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Menoken scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000400
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Appert Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000461
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Braddock scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W1007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000463
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Solberg Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000535
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sibley Butte scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000539
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Stony Slough scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4652.5-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000555
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Sterling scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000556
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Driscoll scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4645-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1975; 000560
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Goodrich SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4715-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1978; 000192
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Goodrich SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722.5-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1978; 000193
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Zeeland scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4552.5-W9945/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1978; 000209
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Goodrich East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4722-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1978; 000422
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wing scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10015/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000210
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Westfield scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000219
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Canfield Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707-W10022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000270
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Regan scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000311
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grass Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000316
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Harriet Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000327
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Harriet Lake SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000328
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Harriet Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000384
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Arena scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4707.5-W10007.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000462
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Baldwin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000479
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Senger Lake N scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000519
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Senger Lake S scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1979; 000520
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hague scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W9952.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000181
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Hague Se scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W9945/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000182
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lynwood scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000196
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Weisser Dam East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W9945/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000223
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Weisser Dam West scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W9952.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000224
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Wabek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000229
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Underdahl Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000236
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fallon scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000250
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fallon NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000251
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Fish Creek scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000252
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Flasher scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000253
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Freda scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W101057.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000262
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Crown Butte Creek NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000282
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Crown Butte Creek SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000283
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Crown Butte Creek SW scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000284
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dogtooth Buttes scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000292